Finding Aid for School of Nursing (University of Michigan) records, 1891-2010
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Dean Rhetaugh Dumas
  - Topical Files (), 1961-1999; bulk 1981-1993
    - Advisory Council, 1974-1977 (Box 47)
    - Affiliation Agreements, 1993 (Box 47)
    - Affirmative Action Committee, 1990-1992 (Box 47)
    - Agent Orange, 1989 (Box 47)
    - AIDS, 1986 (Box 47)
    - Alcohol and Drug Policy, 1993 (Box 47)
    - Alumni Awards, 1958-1973 (Box 47)
    - Alumni Society, 1991-1993 (Box 47)
    - American Association of University Professors-U-M Chapter, 1987 (Box 47)
    - American Journal of Psychiatric Nursing, 1985 (Box 47)
    - Ann Arbor Schools, 1994 (Box 47)
    - Annual Reports
      - 1991-1992 (Box 47)
      - 1990-1991, 2 folders (Box 47)
      - 1989-1990, 2 folders (Box 47)
      - 1988-1989, 2 folders (Box 48)
      - 1987-1988, 3 folders (Box 48)
      - 1986-1987 (Box 48)
      - 1985-1986 (Box 48)
      - 1984-1985, 2 folders (Box 48)
      - 1983-1984, 2 folders (Box 48)
      - 1982-1983, 2 folders (Box 48)
      - 1981-1982, 2 folders (Box 48)
      - 1980-1981, 2 folders (Box 48)
      - 1977-1980 (Box 48)
      - 1975-1977 (Box 48)
      - 1974-1975 (Box 48)
    - Archival Report (Box 49)
      - 1988-1989 (Box 49)
      - 1987-1988 (Box 49)
      - 1985-1987 (Box 49)
      - 1984-1985 (Box 49)
      - 1983-1984 (Box 49)
      - 1982-1983 (Box 49)
      - 1981-1982 (Box 49)
    - Area Chairpersons Meetings, 1981-1982 (Box 49)
    - Awards
      - 1981-1994 (Box 49)
      - 1975-1978 (Box 49)
    - Background Information on Organizational Structure of Peer Schools, 1988 (Box 49)
    - Basic Life Support Certification, 1984-1991 (Box 49)
    - Biochemistry Course, 1992-1993 (Box 49)
    - Biomedical Research Support Grant, 1980-1993 (Box 49)
    - Black Female Leadership, 1988 (Box 49)
    - Briefing Book, 1986 (Box 49)
    - Briefing Book for Dean, 1981 (Box 49)
    - Budget
      - 1993-1994
        - General (Box 49)
        - FTE Requests (Box 49)
        - Salary Program (Box 49)
      - 1992-1993
        - General (Box 49)
        - FTE Requests (Box 49)
        - Salary Program (Box 49)
      - 1991-1992
        - General (Box 49)
        - Conscious Net Support Model (Box 49)
        - FTE Requests (Box 49)
        - Salary Program (Box 49)
      - 1990-1991
        - General (Box 49)
        - FTE Requests (Box 49)
      - 1989-1990
        - General (Box 49)
        - FTE Requests (Box 49)
      - 1988-1989 (Box 50)
        - General, 2 folders (Box 50)
        - FTE Requests (Box 50)
        - Salary Program (Box 50)
      - 1987-1988
        - General (Box 50)
        - FTE Requests (Box 50)
      - 1986-1987 (Box 50)
      - 1985-1986 (Box 50)
      - 1984-1985 (Box 50)
      - 1983-1984, 2 folders (Box 50)
      - 1982-1983, 2 folders (Box 50)
      - 1981-1982 (Box 50)
      - 1980-1981 (Box 50)
      - Budget Reduction Information, 1982; 2 folders (Box 50)
      - "The Evolution of a Budgetary Process at the U-M School of Nursing,", circa 1981 (Box 50)
      - Historical Budget Materials, 1979-1982 (Box 50)
      - Retrenchment Plan, 1980-1982 (Box 50)
    - Budget Priorities Committee-Small Unit Task Force, 1991 (Box 50)
    - Cancer Biology Training Program, 1990-1992 (Box 50)
    - Cancer Center, 1986-1994 (Box 50)
    - Centennial
      - General, 1986-1991; 2 folders (Box 50)
      - Monograph, 1991-1992 (Box 50)
    - Center for Afro-American and African Studies (CAAS), 1983-1991 (Box 51)
    - Center for Gerontological Nursing
      - General, 1981-1990 (Box 51)
      - Annual Meetings, 1988-1991 (Box 51)
        (includes audiocassette)
      - Area Meetings, 1986-1990 (Box 51)
      - Continence Clinic, 1986-1987 (Box 51)
      - Master's Degree Program Proposal, undated 1986 (Box 51)
      - Teaching Nursing Home Project, 1985-1990; 3 folders (Box 51)
    - Center for Nursing Research
      - General
        - 1989-1993, 2 folders (Box 51)
        - 1980-1988, 3 folders (Box 51)
      - Advisory Board, 1991-1992 (Box 51)
      - Annual Meetings, 1987-1993 (Box 51)
      - Guidelines for Grant Preparation, 1993 (Box 51)
    - Center for Research on Learning and Teaching (CRLT)
      - Faculty Development Fund Proposals, 1982-1994 (Box 51)
      - Review Committee, 1983 (Box 51)
      - Teaching Evaluations, 1994 (Box 51)
    - Center for the Education of Women, 1983-1994 (Box 51)
    - Centers of Excellence, 1991-1992 (Box 51)
    - Child-Adolescent Health Behavior Research Center, 1993 (Box 51)
    - Childbearing and Dependent Care, 1989-1991 (Box 51)
    - U-M Children's Center, 1980-1992 (Box 51)
    - Clinical Simulation Laboratory, 1991-1993 (Box 51)
    - Clinical Trials in Nursing Research, 1989 (Box 51)
    - Clinician Teacher Proposal, 1992 (Box 51)
    - Collaborative Activities Between School of Nursing and University Medical Center, 1990 (Box 51)
    - Collaboration with College of Literature, Science and the Arts (LS&A), 1991 (Box 52)
    - College Resources Analysis System (CRAS), 1990-1993 (Box 52)
    - Commencement
      - 1999, 2 videotapes (Box 52)
      - 1994 (Box 52)
      - 1990-1992 (Box 52)
      - 1989 (Box 52)
    - Commencement Proposal, 1988 (Box 52)
    - Commission on the Undergraduate Experience, 1991-1994 (Box 52)
    - Committee for Gender Research, 1982-1983 (Box 52)
    - Committee on Ethics, Humanism and Medicine, 1980-1982 (Box 52)
    - Commonwealth Fund-Executive Nurse Leadership Program, 1983 (Box 52)
    - Community-Based BSN Program for Registered Nurses, 1978 (Box 52)
    - Community Health Nursing
      - General, 1981-1989; 2 folders (Box 52)
      - Annual Meetings, 1985-1991 (Box 52)
      - Faculty Meeting Minutes, 1987-1992; 2 folders (Box 52)
      - Graduate Program Revision, 1986; 2 folders (Box 52)
    - Computer-Based Education in Nursing, 1983 (Box 52)
    - Computing, 1979-1983 (Box 52)
    - Conduct and Utilization of Research in Nursing (CURN), 1975-1980; 2 folders (Box 52)
    - Confidentiality of Personnel Files, 1992 (Box 52)
    - Consortium on Education and Training in Aging (proposed), 1987 (Box 52)
    - Continuing Education, 1980-1982 (Box 52)
    - Corner Health Center, 1982 (Box 52)
    - Course Materials
      - Advanced Study of the Nursing Process, Nursing 515, 1983 (Box 52)
      - Philosophical and Conceptual Foundations for Theory Development in Nursing Practice, Nursing 531, 1988-1992 (Box 52)
      - Nursing Management of Childbearing Families, Nursing 540, 1984 (Box 52)
      - Psychodynamics of Childbearing, Nursing 541, 1984-1985 (Box 52)
      - Physiological Bases of Childbearing, Nursing 542, 1983-1985 (Box 52)
      - History and Politics of Nursing, Nursing 543, 1983 (Box 52)
      - Theoretical Basis of Parent-Child Nursing, Nursing 544, 1983-1984 (Box 52)
      - Nursing Care of Children in Families I, Nursing 546, 1984-1985 (Box 52)
      - Nursing Care of Children in Families II, Nursing 547, 1984 (Box 52)
      - Nursing in Rural and Inner City America, Nursing 561, 1984-1985 (Box 52)
      - Advanced Primary Care Nursing I, Nursing 566, 1989-1992 (Box 52)
      - Empirical Methods of Theory Development in Nursing, Nursing 630, 1991 (Box 52)
      - Clinical Practicum in Perinatal Nursing, Nursing 640, 1983-1984 (Box 52)
      - High Risk Perinatal Nursing, Nursing 641, 1983-1985 (Box 52)
      - Rural Nursing Practicum, Nursing 642, 1984-1986 (Box 52)
      - Nursing Care of Children in Families III, Nursing 646, 1983-1984 (Box 52)
      - Advanced Clinical Practicum, Nursing 648, 1983-1985 (Box 52)
      - Nursing 666, 1991-1992 (Box 52)
      - Advanced Primary Care Nursing of Adults and Groups, Nursing 667, 1992 (Box 52)
      - Synthesis and Application of Community Health Nursing Theories and Practices, Nursing 669, 1990 (Box 53)
      - Strategies in Role Development: Master Nurse Clinician, Nursing 671, 1984-1986 (Box 53)
      - Practicum in Nursing Administration, Nursing 683, 1985 (Box 53)
      - Practicum in Teaching Nursing, Nursing 685, 1984-1985 (Box 53)
      - Practicum in Clinical Specialist, Nursing 688, 1984-1986 (Box 53)
      - Miscellaneous Parent-Child Nursing Syllabi, 1988-1991; 2 folders (Box 53)
    - "Course of Scholarly Development: Turning Points" (by Rhetaugh Dumas), 1988 (Box 53)
    - Cultural Diversity Awareness Seminar with Edwin Nichols, 1993 (Box 53)
    - Database Reports
      - 1992-1994 (Box 53)
      - 1990-1991 (Box 53)
    - Dean's Council
      - 1991-1993, 2 folders (Box 53)
      - 1989-1990, 2 folders (Box 53)
      - 1988-1989, 2 folders (Box 53)
    - Dean's Meetings, 1982 (Box 53)
    - Dean's Meetings with Staff, 1991-1992 (Box 53)
    - U-M Dearborn Cooperative Program, 1989-1990 (Box 53)
    - Dental Service Plan Policy, 1988 (Box 53)
    - Development and Alumni Affairs
      - General, 1986-1994; 4 folders (Box 53)
      - Campaign for Michigan Kickoff, 1992 (Box 53)
      - Capital Campaign, 1990-1991 (Box 53)
      - Centennial Gift
        - Medical School, 1991-1993 (Box 53)
        - University Hospitals, 1990 (Box 53)
      - Friends Scholars Program, 1987-1993; 2 folders (Box 53)
      - Prospects, 1988-1993 (Box 54)
      - University Hospitals, 1988 (Box 54)
      - U-M Alumni Census, 1981 (Box 54)
    - Diabetes Outpatient Education Program, 1990-1994 (Box 54)
    - Discriminatory Harassment Policy, 1988-1989 (Box 54)
    - Distinguished Professorships
      - 1987 (Box 54)
      - 1976-1977 (Box 54)
    - Diversity Retreat, 1987-1988 (Box 54)
    - Diversity Symposium, 1988 (Box 54)
    - Division of Acute, Critical and Long-Term Care Programs
      - General, 1991-1994 (Box 54)
      - Annual Meetings, 1992-1993 (Box 54)
    - Division of Health Promotion and Risk Reduction Programs, 1990-1994 (Box 54)
    - Division of Nursing Systems, 1991 (Box 54)
    - Division of Research Development and Administration (DRDA), 1990-1993 (Box 54)
    - Doctoral Program
      - General, 1982-1983 (Box 54)
      - Faculty Meetings, 1980-1986; 2 folders (Box 54)
      - Minority Students, 1992 (Box 54)
      - Ph.D. Review Committee, 1978 (Box 54)
      - Proposed Revisions, 1984-1986 (Box 54)
      - Review of Proposed Program at Northwestern State University, 1982-1983 (Box 54)
      - Self-Assessment, 1985 (Box 54)
      - Self-Assessment Results, 1989 (Box 54)
      - Steering Committee, 1991-1994 (Box 54)
      - Student Roster, 1984-1988 (Box 54)
      - Students
        - Sau Li, 1989-1990 (Box 73)
          [SR RESTRICTED until July 1, 2065 ]
        - Miscellaneous, 1988-1990 (Box 54)
    - Dumas, Rhetaugh
      - Biographical Information, 1988 (Box 54)
      - C.V.s, undated (Box 54)
      - Miscellaneous Notes and Writings, 1985-1986 (Box 54)
    - Economic Alliance for Michigan, 1988 (Box 54)
    - Editing Assistance, 1988 (Box 54)
    - Elliott, Jo Eleanor, 1989-1990 (Box 54)
    - Employment of Graduates, 1984 (Box 54)
    - Endowment Loan, 1994 (Box 54)
    - Enrollment Management
      - 1993 (Box 54)
      - 1992 (Box 54)
      - 1989-1992 (Box 54)
    - Entry Into Practice, 1980 (Box 54)
    - Ethical Conduct in Scholarship, 1983-1985 (Box 54)
    - Extension Services, 1981-1983 (Box 54)
    - Extension Services Reimbursement, 1992 (Box 55)
    - Fact Sheet, 1987-1990 (Box 55)
    - Faculty Summer Research Fellowships, 1988-1989 (Box 55)
    - Faculty Task Force on Information Technology (FTFIT), 1994 (Box 55)
    - Finance, Vice President for
      - General, 1988-1993 (Box 55)
      - Capital Campaign, 1985-1990 (Box 55)
    - U-M Flint
      - Microwave Transmission Link, 1983 (Box 55)
      - Proposed BSN Program, 1976-1992; 6 folders (Box 55)
      - Proposed Programs, 1991 (Box 55)
    - Freedom of Information/Freedom of Speech, 1977-1985 (Box 55)
    - Freshman Application Analysis, 1988 (Box 55)
    - Fuld Fellowship, 1992-1993 (Box 55)
    - Fundamentals of Nursing Area
      (also known as Basic Concepts and Core)
      - General, 1981-1988 (Box 55)
      - Annual Meeting, 1985-1990 (Box 55)
    - Gehrung Associates University Relations Counselors, 1987-1990 (Box 55)
    - General Counsel, Office of, 1990-1992 (Box 55)
    - Geriatric Center, 1987-1992 (Box 55)
    - Government-University-Industry Research Roundtable (GUIR), 1986 (Box 55)
    - Government Relations, Vice President for, 1984-1992 (Box 55)
    - Graduate Nursing Research Symposium, 1984-1989 (Box 55)
    - Graduate Student Assistants, 1980-1989 (Box 55)
    - Graduate Student Placement in Hospitals, 1985 (Box 55)
    - Graduate Studies
      - Associate Dean for
        - 1990-1991 (Box 55)
        - 1988-1989 (Box 55)
        - 1982-1987, 2 folders (Box 55)
      - Faculty, 1985-1991; 3 folders (Box 55)
      - Master's Program Core Courses, 1989 (Box 55)
      - Open House, 1983-1989 (Box 55)
      - Self-Assessment, 1985 (Box 56)
      - Rackham Report on Quality of Graduate Programs, 1987 (Box 56)
      - Single Master's Degree Proposal, 1986-1990 (Box 56)
    - Group on Sexual Harassment (GOSH), 1992-1993 (Box 56)
    - Health Care Finance Apprenticeship, 1982-1984 (Box 56)
    - Hearing Panels, 1988 (Box 56)
    - Henderson, Virginia, 1988-1990 (Box 56)
    - Hepatitis B Immunization Policy, 1987-1993 (Box 56)
    - Hinshaw, Ada Sue-C.V., undated (Box 56)
    - Historical Center for the Health Sciences, 1988-1994 (Box 56)
    - Historical Perspective on Nursing, undated (Box 56)
    - History and Politics of Nursing, 1979-1982 (Box 56)
    - HIV Exposure Policy, 1992 (Box 56)
    - Honorary Degree Nominations, 1992 (Box 56)
    - Honorary Degree Policy, 1987 (Box 56)
    - Honorary Degrees, 1977-1981 (Box 56)
    - Information List, 1984-1986 (Box 56)
    - Information Systems Integration for the Health Sciences, 1988-1990 (Box 56)
    - Information Technology-Planning and Development, 1988-1992; 2 folders (Box 56)
    - Information Technology, Vice Provost for-General Funds Computing Allocation for MTS, 1989-1994 (Box 56)
    - Information Technology Assessment, 1991-1992 (Box 56)
    - Information Technology Division-Data System Center, 1993 (Box 56)
    - Institute of Gerontology
      - General, 1984-1989 (Box 56)
      - Michigan Geriatric Education Center, 1983-1986 (Box 56)
    - Institutional Training Grant for Pre-and Postdoctoral Training, 1987 (Box 56)
    - Integrated Academic Information Management System, 1987 (Box 56)
    - International Affairs
      - General, 1982-1999 (Box 56)
      - External Nursing Consultants, 1991-1992 (Box 56)
      - Nightingale School Visit, 1982-1983 (Box 56)
    - International Health and Aging Program, 1982-1986 (Box 56)
    - International Institute, 1993 (Box 56)
    - International Nursing Center, 1981-1982 (Box 56)
    - International Women's Decade, 1984 (Box 56)
    - Robert Wood Johnson Foundation, 1989-1990 (Box 56)
    - Joint NDC and Administrative Council, 1987-1988 (Box 56)
    - Jordan, 1993-1994 (Box 56)
    - W.K. Kellogg Foundation
      - General, 1983-1989 (Box 56)
      - Continuing Medical Education Grant, 1987-1992 (Box 56)
      - Leadership Seminar, 1987 (Box 56)
      - National Fellowship Program, 1981-1985 (Box 57)
      - Proposal to Extend Educational Opportunities for Registered Nurses in Michigan, 1981; 2 folders (Box 57)
      - Site Visit Planning, 1985 (Box 57)
    - Martin Luther King Day Celebrations
      - 1989-1994 (Box 57)
      - 1985-1988 (Box 57)
    - Legislative Coordinator, 1982 (Box 57)
    - Literature, Science and the Arts, College of
      - General, 1987-1993 (Box 57)
      - Central Committee on the Undergraduate Experience, 1990-1991 (Box 57)
      - Preferred Admissions, 1985-1986 (Box 57)
    - Long Range Planning, 1983 (Box 57)
    - Long Range Planning Retreat, 1984-1985 (Box 57)
    - MacArthur Chair, 1981 (Box 57)
    - "Managing Administrative Boundaries: The Role of a Dean,", 1990 (Box 57)
    - McLean Hospital-Search Committee for the Director of Nursing, 1983-1984 (Box 57)
    - Medical Affairs, Vice Provost for, 1984-1992 (Box 57)
    - Medical Center
      - General (Box 57)
      - Committee Representation, 1981-1988 (Box 57)
      - HomeMed Research Committee, 1989-1992 (Box 57)
      - Human Resources, 1983-1993 (Box 57)
      - Learning Resource Center, 1980-1994 (Box 57)
      - Memorandum of Understanding Regarding Joint Agreements Between the School of Nursing and Medical Center, 1992 (Box 57)
    - Medical Center Alumni Society
      - General, 1989-1992 (Box 57)
      - Awards, 1985-1993 (Box 57)
      - Board of Governors, 1982-1989 (Box 57)
      - Outreach, 1988-1992 (Box 57)
    - Medical Facilities
      - Bronson Methodist Hospital, 1984 (Box 57)
      - Butterworth Hospital, 1987 (Box 57)
      - Catherine McAuley Health Center, 1985-1989 (Box 57)
      - Chelsea Methodist Retirement Home, 1982-1983 (Box 57)
      - Henry Ford Hospital, 1984-1986; 2 folders (Box 57)
      - Hurley Hospital, 1982 (Box 57)
      - Sisters of Mercy Corporation, 1977-1983 (Box 57)
    - Medical School
      - General, 1982-1993 (Box 57)
      - Dean Search, 1982 (Box 57)
    - Medical-Surgical Nursing
      - General
        - 1985-1990, 2 folders (Box 58)
        - 1981-1983 (Box 58)
      - Annual Meetings, 1985-1991 (Box 58)
      - Faculty Meetings, 1988 (Box 58)
    - Michigan, State of
      - Board of Nursing, 1976-1994; 2 folders (Box 58)
      - Department of
        - Education, 1976 (Box 58)
        - Health and Human Services-Audit, 1991 (Box 58)
        - Mental Health, 1980-1989 (Box 58)
        - Public Health
          - 1984-1994 (Box 58)
          - 1980-1982 (Box 58)
          - Minority Health Advisory Committee, 1988 (Box 58)
          - Women in Health: A New Agenda Conference, 1984 (Box 58)
      - Legislature, 1981-1991 (Box 58)
      - Michigan Essential Health Provider Program, 1989 (Box 58)
      - State Health Plan, 1982-1988; 2 folders (Box 58)
    - Michigan Academy of Science, Arts and Letters, 1980-1988 (Box 58)
    - Michigan Association of Governing Boards Distinguished Faculty Award, 1991-1992 (Box 58)
    - Michigan Committee for Marketing BSN Careers in Nursing, 1988-1989 (Box 58)
    - Michigan Diabetes Research and Training Center, 1985-1992 (Box 58)
    - Michigan Information Technology Network, 1988 (Box 58)
    - Michigan Mandate, 1992 (Box 58)
    - Michigan Nurses Survey, 1989-1991 (Box 58)
    - Michigan Public Health Institute, 1989 (Box 58)
    - Minority Affairs, Office of (School of Nursing)
      - General
        - 1991-1993 (Box 58)
        - 1988-1990 (Box 58)
        - 1980-1984 (Box 58)
      - Area Meeting Minutes, 1988-1990 (Box 58)
      - Roles and Responsibilities, 1992 (Box 58)
    - Minority Concerns Committee of the Health Occupations Council-Report and Recommendations on Nursing, 1982 (Box 58)
    - Minority Student Recruitment, 1981-1987 (Box 58)
    - Minority Student Recruitment Coordinating Committee, 1986-1988 (Box 58)
    - Minority Student Retention, 1991 (Box 58)
    - Mott/Women's/Holden Hospitals, 1983-1989 (Box 58)
    - National Academy of Sciences, 1984-1988 (Box 58)
    - National Center for Nursing Research Specialized Center, 1988-1989 (Box 58)
    - National Council Licensure Examination (NCLEX) Summary Profile, 1993 (Box 59)
    - National Institute for Nursing, 1983-1984; 2 folders (Box 59)
    - National Institutes of Health
      - General, 1980-1991 (Box 59)
      - Advisory Committee to the Director, 1986 (Box 59)
      - Centennial-Symposium: "Nursing Research: Developing the Science of Caring,", 1987 (Box 59)
      - Collaboration with Clinical Center, 1984-1985 (Box 59)
      - Task Force on Nursing Research, 1984 (Box 59)
    - National Nurses Week, 1994 (Box 59)
    - National Review for Nurses, 1984 (Box 59)
    - National Science Foundation, 1981 (Box 59)
    - Natural Resources, School of, 1984-1988 (Box 59)
    - News and Information Services, 1982-1992 (Box 59)
    - North Campus Nursing Clinic, 1992-1994 (Box 59)
    - Nurse-Midwifery Program
      - General, 1982-1994; 4 folders (Box 59)
      - Feasibility and Design, 1986 (Box 59)
      - Proposal, 1987-1988 (Box 59)
    - Nurses for the Future Conference, 1986-1987 (Box 59)
    - Nursing Administration
      - General, 1988-1990; 2 folders (Box 59)
      - Annual Meetings, 1990 (Box 59)
      - Commonwealth Fund, 1989-1991; 2 folders (Box 59)
      - Dual Degree Proposal, 1984 (Box 59)
      - Master of Science Proposal, 1985 (Box 59)
      - Task Force/Advisory Committee, 1988 (Box 59)
    - Nursing and Health Care Systems Administration Programs-Annual Meetings, 1991-1992 (Box 59)
    - Nursing and Health Organizations
      - American Association of Colleges of Nursing (AACN)
        - General (Box 59)
        - Generic Baccalaureate Nursing Data Project, 1984-1986 (Box 59)
        - Governmental Affairs Committee, 1983-1985 (Box 59)
        - Questionnaires and Surveys, 1986-1993; 2 folders (Box 60)
      - American Medical Association-Health Policy Agenda Project, 1982-1986 (Box 60)
      - American Nurses' Association
        - General (Box 60)
        - Minority Fellowship Program, 1982-1991 (Box 60)
        - Nominations to Offices, 1983-1984 (Box 60)
      - American Nurses' Foundation (Box 60)
      - American Public Health Association, 1984 (Box 60)
      - Association of Black Nursing Faculty (Box 60)
      - Committee on Institutional Cooperation (CIC)
        - General, 1993-1994 (Box 60)
        - Nursing Deans, 1982-1994; 2 folders (Box 60)
      - International Council of Nurses, 1979-1983 (Box 60)
      - Michigan American Council on Education National Identification Project (ACE NIP)
        - General, 1977-1986; 2 folders (Box 60)
        - Minority Liaison, 1982-1983 (Box 60)
      - Michigan Association of Colleges of Nursing (MACN)
        - General
          - 1991-1994 (Box 60)
          - 1988-1990 (Box 60)
          - 1986-1988, 2 folders (Box 60)
          - 1982-1985, 3 folders (Box 60)
        - Membership and Surveys, 1983-1993 (Box 60)
        - Proposal for a Statewide Mechanism for Advancing Nursing Education
          - General, 1982-1988 (Box 60)
          - Background, 1988-1989 (Box 60)
        - Retreat, 1986 (Box 60)
      - Michigan Council of Collegiate Nursing School Administrators (MCCNA), 1981-1982; 2 folders (Box 60)
      - Michigan Health Care Education and Research Foundation-Grants Advisory Committee, 1985-1986 (Box 60)
      - Michigan Hospital Association, 1985 (Box 60)
      - Michigan League for Nursing, 1977-1993 (Box 60)
      - Michigan Nurses Association
        - 1984-1992 (Box 61)
        - 1981-1983 (Box 61)
      - Michigan Nursing Students Association, 1989 (Box 61)
      - Michigan Research Corporation, 1982 (Box 61)
      - Midwest Nursing Research Society (MNRS), 1981-1993 (Box 61)
      - National Black Nurses' Association, 1983-1993 (Box 61)
      - National League for Nursing
        - General, 1981-1993 (Box 61)
        - Accreditation
          - 1992-1993 (Box 61)
          - Self-Study, 1993 (Box 61)
          - 1984-1986, 2 folders (Box 61)
          - Self-Study, 1985; 2 volumes (Box 61)
          - 1979 (Box 61)
          - Self-Evaluation, 1977; 2 volumes (Box 61)
        - Membership Materials, 1961-1994 (Box 61)
        - Video Taping on Psychiatric Mental Health Nursing, 1992-1993 (Box 61)
      - National Mental Health Association, 1984-1986 (Box 61)
      - Nurse Faculty Research Development in the Midwest (NFRDM), 1981 (Box 61)
      - Nurses' Corporation of America, 1985-1987 (Box 61)
      - Nurses Political Action Committee, 1984 (Box 61)
      - Nursing Research Roundtable, 1988 (Box 61)
      - Sigma Theta Tau, 1983-1993; 2 folders (Box 61)
      - Statewide Health Coordinating Council, 1983-1985 (Box 61)
      - "Think Tank" Group, 1982 (Box 61)
      - Visiting Nurse Association, 1983 (Box 61)
      - Western Council on Higher Education in Nursing, 1987 (Box 61)